what up guys is Kobe town
oh oh you saw the the Android kernel a
eco all the leaks and found the leaks
alright let's just yo black people we
judge on test now
alright so I've had a chance to watch a
few of your videos and we're gonna watch
them with you and we're gonna look at
them now you guys know what the judgment
criteria was we can
a can of a fair contest without rules
don't smash your tennis racket on the
ground video theme is increasing open
pilot daily active users so that's
really what we're looking for we're
looking for videos that are likely to
increase the number of users that open
pilot hats so if we're going straight
off of likes it seems like Dewayne
LaRose won with 14 but we can't do it
just based on likes how fair would that
be
especially since two of them got
retweeted and the time needed was
different okay so who do you guys think
won say say say me uh in the in the
periscope comments who you think we
should give the prize to and maybe I'll
just agree with some of you and then we
don't have to judge anything that would
be kinda nice for it uh Jeffrey Nichols
is that you you can't say your own name
you liked Chris's the one who used it
safely okay so we have Jeffrey Nichols
we have Chris's we have mr. Kaul we have
another vote for Chris I let's watch
Chris's first right here open pilot is
an advanced driver assistance to
surprise Winky pick a function from this
to this as well as provide smoother and
safer radar adaptive cruise control open
pilot allows you to be driving
hands-free and feet free for long
periods of time without intervention
even more so on interstates and highways
look it's Canadian model but how does
this all work you need three pieces of
hardware all bought from comma a I slash
shop first
the giraffe this device look at my
watching the product I like into a more
Universal port for the next piece of
hardware which is the great panda panda
you see I'm not I feel about that ant
could also send information as well
James today tomorrow man Sharp's is
speed up slow down and turn the wheel in
either direction it also has a
high-precision GPS antenna used to
create HD maps as you drive finally the
e on this is the main device that drives
your car first plug into the panda then
mounted on your window look at that nice
long gate your car an existing radar
information which shows exactly how far
away the car in front of you is cut into
it for speed up its prey Pro guys it
also has a high quality camera that
looks for lane lines in the road and
tells the wheel to stay exactly centered
in the lane lines at all times as an
added bonus it is also a fantastic
dashcam with free unlimited cloud
storage open pilot runs at Honda's
Toyota's Acuras Lexus GM in hyundais
with even more car support being worked
on every day and the best part
altogether this setup costs less than a
thousand dollars checked up your
existing car is compatible then go buy
an e on panda enter app today and
upgrade your car to the future
alright so that's that's that's
definitely a contender for the price we
did get a few votes for mr. Cole's video
now we can't really judge it based on
likes because I didn't retweet this one
I didn't actually see it heard of
self-driving cars
they'll drive us from point A to point G
don't learn how we look at those Tesla's
they look pretty nice he gets a point
for nice looking tests how can these
self-driving cars learn how we the
majority drive and only the wealthiest
minorities
[Music]
and the best part is every time I Drive
a pilot today you don't need the 88
Tesla the way Moe or the Cadillac ct-6
and it's ready to start making driving
safer it's not an IRL I've been testing
oh he's sitting in the chair first check
your car's compatibility by heading over
to thanks for watching mmm give Baseball
America's past-time that's that's
exactly how I feel watching this 343
views 581 views mmm
okay all right who else do we have as a
contender who's a serious contender I
would say as far as actual information
goes Chris's does does win out um I did
really like this video I think that the
execution wasn't quite there but I
really liked the concept ideas for ideas
for future like so once I'm here I don't
know which ones open pilot and which
ones the original um it would also be
cool to see a counter like counting up
every time they make mistakes so this
video certainly gets an honorable
mention for concept and if we have
another video contest clean up the
execution
look yours Danijela oh just box I hate
the bots alright what else we got here
what was this is this over bah what is
all this stuff steering and acceleration
it integrates directly with I don't
think it's unsafe for the camera to be
held by the driver if that's your say
and radar system nice great panda magic
it's not unsafe guys
the car in front and automatically break
it will detect the car to the left and
overtake when we're judging the video
contest who do you think won we watched
virtually Chris's and mr. Coles they
were both very good yeah see what we got
here he also talks you so I was born I
do like the music choice
the 360p leaves something to be desired
nice iPhone X advertisements
[Music]
okay guys any any any last videos to
watch Oh video contest judging wow
that's so exciting what's going on Wow
hey I don't know if I'm blaming Europe
I'm blaming Twitty oh can you package
this as a rearview mirror with no but
you can all right guys let's let's put
it's either gonna be Chris or mr. Cole
let's let's put them up next to each
other side by side right here look at
yours but it's not a winner all right
all right guys I think I think I've made
up my mind I think we have a winner I
think you guys already know well
splitting the pie what is that man it's
not like everybody gets to get high no
I'll split the pot
ha yes yes yes yes she says oh and and
and oh wow Wow I gave I gave a great the
winner
what is open pilot by virtually Chris I
love the product shots
I love the touching look look at that
touching of the product look at look at
the touching oh it's so good yeah I know
this show it's falling apart it's old
I love the touching I love how it shows
off all the products mr. Cole you are
the runner-up I love how the chair is
brought through the whole video here's
the chair or was the scene when you sit
on the chair all that is a great that is
a great scene I must say for artistic
purposes we give it a mr. Cole but our
product our conscious is of course the
theme is increasing daily active unit
users so so it is it is virtually Chris
for the win we will be hooking him up
with $1,000 1,000 should we do cash we
get $1,000 cash no way no way we can't
do that the tax man gets angry $1,000
for the win and mr. Cole you will be
receiving the last the absolute last
ultra-rare come a IBT reach out to
support a common AI with your address
and Chris will get a check and mr. Cole
will get a beanie okay thank you for
watching
periscope where we judge the video as
promised we deliver on our promises
speaking about promises we got HD maps
by the end of the year we're gonna get
to 1,000 daily active users and okay
final two of us in their October first
new product announcement by eelain's all
right thank you very much